http://www.unb.ca/privacy/

Web privacy statement
The University of New Brunswick is committed to protecting your personal information.
Personal information is not collected automatically
Personal information is not automatically collected from you when you visit UNB’s website. You may choose to provide personal information via web form or email when applying for a university service or when using our web feedback form. Any personal information that you provide will be protected in accordance with applicable privacy laws and UNB policy.Additionally, members of the UNB community may log in to secure pages, using their unique UNB login ID. The UNB login ID may be stored in a log along with the uniform resource locator of the secure page(s) that were visited.
Information gathered automatically
UNB's web server logs some information about Internet traffic on its pages. These logs capture aggregate, generic, non-personal identifying information about visitors such as the type of browser used, pages visited and duration of stay. This information is used to help us understand our Internet traffic and improve our website. The information is only shared between university staff and, at times, between university staff and those responsible for UNB-hosted websites.In some cases, the Internet Protocol (IP) address of visitors could allow for individual identification. Please check with your Internet Service Provider to learn more about how they use IP addresses.
myUNB
Our myUNB section uses cookies, small pieces of information sent from our site to your web browser. Cookies enable our website to remember personal page view settings. This information is used solely to provide an improved experience for our users. Each browser allows you to set your preferences for accepting or rejecting cookies, as well as for deleting cookies. The IT Service Desk can help you find these settings in your browser.
Want to know more?
For more information, or if you have questions or concerns regarding the protection of personal privacy at UNB, see Right to Information and Protection of Privacy or consult the University Secretariat, University of New Brunswick, PO Box 4400, Fredericton, NB, E3B 5A3, (506) 453-4613.
Resources
About UNB
Campus Maps
Campus Security
Careers at UNB
Conference Services
Libraries
Online & Continuing Ed
